<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="app_name">CryptoHQ</string>
  <string name="currency">Currency</string>
  <string name="about">About</string>
  <string name="terms_of_service">Terms of Service</string>
  <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
  <string name="about_description">CryptoHQ is your ultimate crypto tracking app designed to keep you informed about the ever-changing world of cryptocurrencies. With its powerful features including market prices, a comprehensive overview of the biggest gainers and losers, coin details, personalized watch list, and a handy converter, CryptoHQ is your go-to companion for staying updated in the crypto market.</string>
  <string name="about_coin_details_description">Coin Details: Dive into the world of cryptocurrencies with our extensive coin details section. Get access to comprehensive information about thousands of coins, including market capitalization, trading volume, historical data, and key statistics. Stay informed and make informed investment decisions.</string>
  <string name="about_watch_list_description">Watch List: Create your own personalized watch list to monitor your favorite coins. Keep track of their performance and receive timely updates on price fluctuations. CryptoTrackr allows you to effortlessly manage and monitor your investments.</string>
  <string name="about_converter_description">Converter: Simplify your crypto calculations with our intuitive converter. Easily convert any cryptocurrency into your preferred fiat currency or switch between different digital assets. Our converter ensures accurate and convenient value assessments.</string>
  <string name="about_market_description">Market Prices: Stay up-to-date with market prices. CryptoTrackr provides you with live market data, ensuring you are aware of the latest trends and price movements.</string>
  <string name="about_gainers_losers_description">Biggest Gainers and Losers: Stay informed about the most significant price changes in the market. CryptoTrackr highlights the biggest gainers and losers, helping you identify potential investment opportunities or market trends. Gain valuable insights into the performance of different cryptocurrencies.</string>
  <string name="about_credits_description">We would like to acknowledge the following third-party SDKs, APIs, and tools that were instrumental in building CryptoHQ:</string>
  <string name="coingecko_credits">For Cryptocurrencies API (details, market prices and historical data)</string>
  <string name="coingecko">CoinGecko</string>
  <string name="icons8">Icons8</string>
  <string name="icons8_credits">For Icons and images</string>
  <string name="empty_state_illustrator">Muhammad Aqsath Faza</string>
  <string name="empty_state_illustrator_credits">For empty state illustrations</string>
  <string name="vico">Vico</string>
  <string name="vico_credits">For price charts</string>
</resources>